var questions = [
    {
        question: "On which soap opera does Joey have a recurring role as Dr. Drake Ramoray?",
        choices: ["Days of Our Lives", "All My Children", "General Hospital", "The Bold and the Beautiful"],
        answer: "Days of Our Lives"
    },
    {
        question: "How many categories for towels does Monica have?",
        choices: ["12", "20", "11", "8"],
        answer: "11"
    },
    {
        question: "To whom is Joey and Chandler’s TV Guide addressed?",
        choices: ["MR. CHANDELIER BANG", "MISS CHANANDLER BONG", "MS. JOESPHINE TRIBECA", "JOSEPH TRIBIANI"],
        answer: "MISS CHANANDLER BONG"
    },
    {
        question: "What is Phoebe’s twin sister’s name?",
        choices: ["URSULA BUFFAY", "LESLIE BUFFAY", "CHRISSY BUFFAY", "REGINA PHALANGE"],
        answer: "URSULA BUFFAY"
    },
    {
        question: "What color is the couch that the friends sit on at Central Perk?",
        choices: ["Green", "Red", "Orange", "Brown"],
        answer: "Orange"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of Joey and Chandler’s pet duck?",
        choices: ["Bruce", "Melvin", "Duck", "Marcel"],
        answer: "Duck"
    },
    {
        question: "Where were the opening credits filmed?",
        choices: ["BROOKYN, NY", "NEW YORK CITY, NY", "BURBANK, CA", "LOS ANGELES, CA"],
        answer: "BURBANK, CA"
    },
    {
        question: "What was the name of the barista-turned-manager of Central Perk?",
        choices: ["Tyler", "Gunther", "Bobby", "Michael"],
        answer: "Gunther"
    },
    {
        question: "Who was the only cast member to get snubbed by the Emmy’s?",
        choices: ["David Schwimer", "Lisa Kudrow", "Matthew Perry", "Cortney Cox"],
        answer: "Cortney Cox"
    },
    {
        question: "Who sings the theme song?",
        choices: ["R.E.M", "THE CAST", "THE REMBRANDTS", "THE B-52'S"],
        answer: "THE REMBRANDTS"
    },
];
